goucher.edu 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy | Goucher College

This policy explains what types of personal information will be gathered when you visit the Goucher College website, and how this information will be used. 

Some of the college’s departments and centers have more detailed privacy policies or provide additional information relating to their activities, which will supersede or supplement this Privacy Policy. See: 

  * Admissions
  * Institutional Effectiveness

## Information collected

On some parts of the website you may encounter forms that ask you to provide personal information in order to enable the provision of certain services. For example, you may provide information to complete an application for admission or a credit card transaction; to complete a donation form or a request for information form; or to request a Goucher publication. You may provide a name, email address, residential address, phone number and other personal data. 

By supplying this information you are consenting to the college holding and using it for the purposes for which it was provided. Information provided will be kept for as long as is necessary to fulfil that purpose. 

## How the information collected is used

Personal information that you provide to the college will only be used for the purposes stated when the information is requested. 

We may reveal personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third parties: 

  * if you request or authorize it;

  * if the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you, such as enabling you to complete a donation to the college; 

  * if the information is provided to comply with the law;

  * If the information is necessary to protect your health and safety or the health and safety of others; 

  * if the information is provided to our vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or 

  * as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

Personal information will not be sold to third parties, or provided to direct marketing companies or other such organizations without your permission. 

We may share information that does not personally identify you without restriction.

## How we store information collected

Information that you provide to us will ordinarily be stored on our secure servers. However, we do work with third party contractors, some of whom host and operate certain features of the website. Accordingly, information that we collect from you may be maintained onsite or offsite “in the cloud.” That information may be processed by staff who work for us or for one of our contractors. By submitting personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

## How we use "cookies"

Most of our web pages use "cookies". A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we place on your computer or mobile device. These cookies allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website, which helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allow us to improve our website. 

For more detailed information on the cookies we use on the College’s main web pages and the purposes for which we use them, please see our Cookie Statement. 

## Access to information

You may have the right to access information held about you. In addition, if you reside in the European Union you may have other rights granted by the GDPR. These include, but are not limited to, the rights of access to your data; the right to receive your data in portable form; erasure of data; and correction of data. For details see: <https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection_en>

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email. 

## Contact

If you wish to have your information removed from our records, please use this form to [opt out](https://iapp.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/65ac2f10-a690-4904-81f0-c61f77fd34d7). 

Any queries or concerns about privacy on this website should be sent to [webmaster@goucher.edu](mailto:webmaster@goucher.edu).
